Finding Aid for Safety Dept. (University of Michigan) photograph collection, 1969-1970
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Safety Dept. (University of Michigan) photograph collection 1969-1970
University of Michigan. Safety Dept.
0.3
92138 Bimu B27 2
Surveillance-type and other photos of student demonstrations at the University of Michigan.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Donor number 6497.
No further additions to the collection are expected..
The collection is open without restriction.
Public safety department of the University of Michigan involved in investigation of student protest activities.
Photographs and negatives, 1969-1970, showing student unrest on the University of Michigan campus and nearby. Includes protests over interviews conducted on campus, Black Action movement, the ROTC takeover, vandalism and other demonstrations of protest.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Black Action Movement (University of Michigan); Demonstrations--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; University of Michigan--Buildings.; University of Michigan--Campus.; University of Michigan--Students.; University of Michigan--Students--Political activity.; University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs--1961-1970.; Vandalism.; Classrooms--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Student registration.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Photographs
  (Dates of photos indicate printing date and not necessarily the date of the activity shown.)
  - Administration Building, activities near, March 19, 1970 (Folder 1)
  - Angell Hall, March 24, 1970 (Folder 2)
  - Black Action movement, March 1970 (Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 4)
  - Naval Science protest (Folder 5)
  - Interview protests at B.A. (and Engineering?) (Folder 6)
  - Registration (Folder 7)
  - ROTC takeover, September 14, 1969 (photos dated May, 1970) (Folder 8)
  - Tent City, photos dated September 23, 1970 (Folder 9)
  - South U. demonstrations (Folder 10)
  - Vandalism (Folder 11)
  - IST (Institute for Science and Technology) Building bomb damage (Folder 12)